Tech-savvy Lead Developer with proficiency in Javascript, Arduino, Python and Wordpress. Well-trained and experienced with 2 years in software development industry.

Excellent in Graphics Designing consistently creates skilled, clear and brand-specific designs. Demonstrated success in project management and team leadership.

Knowledgeable about viral social media marketing across wide range of platforms. Dedicated to increase knowledge and optimizing personal skills.

# **Work History**

2020-04

**Lead Developer** 

- 2021-07

Superfolio, Dar es Salaam

Developed a financial Assistance Chatbot

2020-11

Web Developer and Designer

- 2021-07

Home Tutor, Dar es Salaam

• Worked collaboratively in team environment to make a website.

2021-06

**Graphics Designer & Web Developer** 

- present

MR.German Restaurant

· Currently developing their website

2021-09

**Software Developer Intern** 

- present

Inalipa

### **Education**

2012-01 Tusiime Primary School

- 2012-12

2012-01

Feza Primary School, Dar es Salaam

- 2014-09

Feza Boys Secondary School, Dar es Salaam

2015-01 - 2018-12

2019-08

Mathematics, Information Technology, Economics,

- 2021-07

**English General** 

Dar es Salaam Independent School , Dar es Salaam

# **Leadership Positions**

2016-01 School Robotics Club Leader

- 2018-12

2020-01 School Media Team Leader

- 2021-07

# Fredy German Mgimba



## **Personal Info**

#### **Email**

fredgerman30@gmail.com

#### **Phone**

+255745676696

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/fdagreat

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fredygerman-mgimba-174081146/

#### Website

mrgreat.greatcompanies.org

## Skills

Leadership

**Teamwork** 

Problem solving

Public speaking and Debating

# **Volunteering & Community Service**

2018-12 - 2021-07	Program Organiser - Feza Alumni Foundation
2020-02	Organising Team - Albinism Charity Walk
2020-01 - 2021-07	IT Crew - Mito Ya Baraka Church (Youtube Analyst)
2021-06	Developer - Prom 2021
	Developed a ticket management system.

# **Certificates & Achievements**

**Honorable Mentioned Certificate (Robotics) - Genius Olympiad** 

Winner - 2021 Dar Open Debate Competition

**Gold Certificate Owlipiad (Science and Technology)** 

**Gold Certificate Gisu Tech Robotics** 

Dar Open Debate Competition (Winning team & top 5 Debater)

Mimi Ni Nani Leadership Development Program.

## **Other Skills**

Web development

Machine Learning

**Chatbot Development** 

Snapchat Lense Designer

Salesperson

Turkish

# Languages

English ★★★★
Swahili ★★★★